postclass.com 2012-03-30

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

At PostClass.com we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by PostClass.com. 

**Information we collect and how we use it**

We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, such as Classified Ads Search. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

  * **Information you provide** – When you sign up for a PostClass.com Account or other PostClass.com service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password), and maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. For certain services, such as you post classified ads, we may release your personal information (not including an account password).  

  * **Cookies** – When you visit PostClass.com, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends.  

  * **Log information** – When you access PostClass.com services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.  

  * **User communications** – When you send email or other communications to PostClass.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.  

  * **Other sites** – This Privacy Policy applies to PostClass.com services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results, sites that include PostClass.com applications, products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.  

PostClass.com only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

PostClass.com processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services.

**Choices for personal information**

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some PostClass.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case PostClass.com may not be able to provide those services to you.

**Information sharing**

PostClass.com only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of PostClass.com in the following limited circumstances: 

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.  

  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  

  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of PostClass.com, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.   

If PostClass.com becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to PostClass.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

**Data integrity**

PostClass.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

**Accessing and updating personal information**

When you use PostClass.com services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page.
